Can you believe it’s been 10 years
since How Not to Die was published?
Well, I’m thrilled to announce
that an updated 10th anniversary
edition of the classic
is being published this December.
15 chapters and each of the
leading 15 causes of death,
talking about the role diet may play
in preventing, arresting, or
reversing each of our top 15 killers,
along with practical tools
like my traffic light system
and the Daily Dozen
to help you eat healthier.
And the revised edition
has all the juicy stuff
that's been published
in the last decade
like Dr. Ornish's
Alzheimer's study
or things we'd like to
forget, like COVID-19,
and the latest on cannabis,
and on down the list.
To find out how to
preorder your copy today,
visit nutritionfacts.org/books.